[Music]
talk about you about
me the
world
all don't
[Music]
be be the
one don'tan
beuse
[Music]
youain just
wan you
again it can make it it you try and i
know the reasons why
you can make it if you only
[Music]
try not left st and there's no one left
to you can make if
[Music]
you
about
you about
[Applause]
me the
world
[Music]
don't
go don'tan
be cause you
[Music]
pain just
w you
[Music]
again you can make it if you try and i
know the reasons why you can make it if
you don't
try not not left the stage and there's
no one else to
bl you can make it you don't
try they don't
understand they don't play this
hand they don't understand
they don't play
this as you watch the  day go by and you
rning out of time you  can make it you
don't last was left
the
and
to can make it if you only
tr if you
[Music]
only